I'm late. Sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
What is the color of your soul?
What color is the color?
Oh, oh.
Hey, I'm not going to get
over as soon as I can.
And it's too strong to run away from me.
Let's see, let's see, once again.
I don't know if it's true, but
I don't know if it's true. I
don't
know
if it's true,
but I don't know if it's true.
Go.
Wow.
As I was landing I saw some old ruins.
They're down the road
about five clicks south.
Looked like a good place to make
a stand and not get surrounded.
We'll all up there then.
The vr mmo community
in the states is huge.
I think this is all that
we're available now.
If we beat them, maybe whoever's behind
this will think twice about sending more.
All right then, I'll bomb
the heck out of them.
Oh by the way, um, is
it okay if I see kirito?
What are you asking permission for?
Of course it's okay.
He's here in the wagon.
Oh he is then.
I guess I'll go in and say hi.
Lady Solus? Huh?
Sorry, I'm not who you think I am.
I'm just borrowing this
outfit for a little bit.
My name's Sinon.
That's right.
I'm from the real world, too.
Just like Asuna.
And Kirito, too.
I'm his friend. Really?
You are, too, huh?
So many women friends.
And he's got even more back home.
Your soul might be broken and you
might not remember who you were,
but all your friends do.
There, can you feel that?
It's the Kirito I remember.
The sarcastic prankster,
stubborn and sometimes immature,
and the strongest, most
kind person I ever knew.
Don't worry.
He'll be back and better than ever!
And in the nick of time, as usual?
Right, Asuna?
Well, I'll be back in a bit.
I want to check those ruins out.
Make sure they're really safe.
I'll fly right back and
let you know if they are.
Wait, hold on.
Did I hear that right?
Can you?
You know, fly?
They said the Solus
account had the power to.
And there's no time
limit on it or anything.
Don't worry about us then.
You have to get Alice back.
The Emperor's got her now.
If you hurry, you can catch them!
Men.
What were we fighting for?
For this?
Why'd you all have to die for them?
Oh, jeez!
I always have the worst
luck with new gear.
Don't you look at me!
Hang on.
Let me straighten up.
Ah, that's better.
Good afternoon, or morning.
You're human.
You should be scared of me.
But you're not.
Of course I'm not.
Why would I be scared of another human?
What are you saying? I...
I'm no human.
Something wrong with your eyes?
Can't you see I'm orc?
What you white humans called big people.
You're human as far as I can tell.
I mean, you're standing there talking,
so that pretty much makes you human.
What are you up to?
Never mind.
Do you know where we are?
Oops, I'm sorry.
I forgot to ask your name.
My name is Lil' Pillan.
Lil' Pillan?
I like it.
It's so unique.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Leafa.
Human.
I don't care what your name is.
You're my prisoner now, and
I'm taking you to the Emperor.
Is this Emperor of yours
also the Dark God Vecta?
Y-yeah?
Okie dokie.
I'll let you take me to him.
talking makes me human this girl's weird
the goblins ogres and giants can all talk
too but humans treat a lot of us like we
lower than dirt all the
same so why don't she
come on
What's going on?
It's D .I .L!
The smell!
Oh, the smell!
The scent of life is strong in this one
yes you've captured a wonderful specimen!
Indeed well done little
pink person well done to
celebrate I shall reward
you with some entertainment!
I
assume you've
never seen
a human woman's body before
this must be quite the
treat for your piggy eyes!
But the fun is only
starting keep watching.
Ah!
System call!
Transfer human unit durability.
Left to self!
Oh, delicious.
Her life is so thick and sweet.
Hey, you let her go!
That eel is my prisoner.
I was gonna take her to the emperor.
Silence, filthy wretch!
Have you forgotten that His Majesty
put all of His forces under my command?
My will is His will.
And as long as I live,
you will obey my orders.
I don't believe it.
Oh, her life surges, it
is overflowing again.
This is mine, life is mine forever.
I can't die here, but she can.
I don't want to kill an Underworld.
Leave her alone.
Leave her alone!
What?
Was that an order?
Are you out of your mind?
Know your place, Piggy.
She is my prisoner now.
And whether I decide to suck the life from
her or snap her neck
is no concern of yours.
On second thought, you
were the one who found her,
so perhaps a slight
concession is in order.
But only if you strip
naked before me right now.
What did you say?
Ever since I first saw you strutting
around in those ridiculous garments,
I was so repulsed I quite nearly gagged.
A mere pig trying to pass as human.
Strip for me get down
on all fours and squeal
and then perhaps I might
let you have her back.
You're human as far as I can tell I
mean you're standing there talking?
Don't.
I'm fine.
I can take it.
But really, it's not worth it.
Go on, pig. Stir it.
Or are you having second thoughts?
Perhaps the sight of her in this state
arouses you and you're too ashamed too.
I'm up. I'm up.
I'm...
I'm a human!
You rotten treasonous swine!
You dare raise your weapon against me?
I'll chop you up into little chunks!
Mix your carcass with hay!
That made you to the board!
How can a human slash
another human to save a pig?
You're evil, and I'll
slash evil to save a human!
Please keep an eye on
Kirito while I'm gone.
Yes, ma 'am.
We'll keep him safe no matter what.
We won't let anyone near him.
We'll guard him with our lives.
Don't worry.
We won't let the enemy get this far in.
No! Attack!
Let's go.
Man, she's vicious when
she's got her game face on.
Racking up the kills
like there's no tomorrow.
He's not slowing down.
I'm switching dragons and
I still can't catch him.
He must have the power to
heal his dragon's life.
That settles it.
Time-splitting sword.
You're a sorry dragon.
Poragiri!
Or her giddy slashes the past.
Whoever that bastard is,
he can't rewind time.
If I get cut down, head back
to the others and help them.
Emperor Vecta, not all
real-worlders are demons like you.
That Asuna girl's proof of that.
You whipped up the Dark Territory
and drove its people to war.
You caused the deaths of tens
of thousands of them, and us.
As far as humans go, that right
there's proof you're evil to the core.
You're gonna pay.
You're gonna feel the
weight of every life lost.
So help me.
How did you pay?
Slippery bastard!
Time splitting.
Sword Karagiri!
You can absorb incarnate abilities.
Is that what it's called incarnate
your fusion of mind and will?
Yours tastes like a
vintage wine rich thick
heavy with a finish that
lingers a bit. Too long.
It's not my favorite, but as a palate
cleanser before the main course, it's not bad.
Come on, let me drink more.
You choke on it!
What's happening?
I was about to do something, but I forgot.
What the hell?
I can't believe I let my
mind wander like that.
You bastard.
You leashed my incarnate
ability right out of my sword.
That was a nifty trick
you pulled just now.
But if we can't cross swords, we're
going to be here all day, your highness.
True.
That reminds me, I have
another trick to try.
You've got to be kidding me.
He clouded my mind just
by pointing a sword at me.
How can I counter that?
I used Karagiri and that didn't work.
The only other skill I got is Ura-Giri.
But he's not going to stand
there as I fire it up.
Have you ever felt you were going to die?
If this is where it's supposed to
happen, I'll make it count, my lady.
Kiddo.
I don't know if I did it right, but I'd
try to be some kind of father to you.
I can't even remember mine,
so it's not like I had a clue as
to what being a dad's all about.
But there's one thing I do know.
A good father would give
his life to protect his kid.
And that's something you're
never gonna understand.
You must have!
God, this game sucks so much ass.
Might as well log out and go back to...
As long as I can stand,
I'm going to keep fighting.
So come on, if you dare.
I can do this all day
if I have to. Get her!
Oh, no. There's more.
That was...
a sword skill.
No way!
Hey there.
Sorry for the wait. You okay?
Klein?
Thank you so
much for watching.
After the night,
I'm scared to be afraid of you?
In this sweet world, I'll see you soon!
See you
next
time.